[{"answer": " Now that I have my own apartment, Im thinking about getting a pet", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Oh, really?  What kind", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Now that I have my own apartment, Im thinking about getting a pet", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Im not sure yet.  Im still deciding.  I really like dogs a lot, especially big ones", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Oh, really?  What kind", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Have you ever had a dog before", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Im not sure yet.  Im still deciding.  I really like dogs a lot, especially big ones", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " No.  We werent allowed to have pets growing up", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Have you ever had a dog before", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well, we had dogs when I was growing up.  Let me just tell you, they are a lo", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 16, "question": " No.  We werent allowed to have pets growing up", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " But it seems like it would be so much fun to have a dog", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Well, we had dogs when I was growing up.  Let me just tell you, they are a lo", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Dont get me wrong, it is a lot of fun.  But dogs eat a lot, you have to was", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " But it seems like it would be so much fun to have a dog", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " True.  That is a lot of work, but I dont think Id mind", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Dont get me wrong, it is a lot of fun.  But dogs eat a lot, you have to was", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " What about your apartment?  Do they allow dogs", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 25, "question": " True.  That is a lot of work, but I dont think Id mind", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " They do.  Id have to pay a non-refundable pet-fee though", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 29, "question": " What about your apartment?  Do they allow dogs", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Id be careful about getting a big dog if I were you.  They like to run aroun", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 30, "question": " They do.  Id have to pay a non-refundable pet-fee though", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " I guess I need to think about that", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Id be careful about getting a big dog if I were you.  They like to run aroun", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " And another thing.  What about the weekends?  You go out of town ever", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": " I guess I need to think about that", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " You", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " And another thing.  What about the weekends?  You go out of town ever", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No way!  Not every weekend!  Youd have to put them in a kennel and tha", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " You", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " I guess there are a lot of things that I didnt think of about getting a dog.  I wa", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " No way!  Not every weekend!  Youd have to put them in a kennel and tha", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " I know.  Puppies are so cute and there are a lot of benefits to having a dog.  ", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I guess there are a lot of things that I didnt think of about getting a dog.  I wa", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Youre probably right.  Maybe I should start with something easier for my first pet", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 54, "question": " I know.  Puppies are so cute and there are a lot of benefits to having a dog.  ", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Fish", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Youre probably right.  Maybe I should start with something easier for my first pet", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " No.  Fish are too boring", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Fish", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " A snake", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 57, "question": " No.  Fish are too boring", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ew!  No!  Snakes are gross", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 58, "question": " A snake", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " A cat", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Ew!  No!  Snakes are gross", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Yeah, maybe a cat would be good.  Do you think a cat would be easier to tak", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " A cat", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Oh, definitely.  With a cat, you just feed them and thats pretty much it.  The", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yeah, maybe a cat would be good.  Do you think a cat would be easier to tak", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " What about on the weekends when I go away", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Oh, definitely.  With a cat, you just feed them and thats pretty much it.  The", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " If its just for a day or two, it shouldnt be a problem.  Just leave enough foo", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " What about on the weekends when I go away", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": "It sounds like a cat would definitely be easier than a dog.  Maybe Ill do that.  Il", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 77, "question": " If its just for a day or two, it shouldnt be a problem.  Just leave enough foo", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " I think a cat would be a great first pet for you.  You could get a cute little kitten", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 79, "question": "It sounds like a cat would definitely be easier than a dog.  Maybe Ill do that.  Il", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " All right.  Ive decided.  Ill get a kitten.  Want to come look for one with me thi", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 79, "question": " I think a cat would be a great first pet for you.  You could get a cute little kitten", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Sure.  I love kittens too", "docId": "07-04", "aSentId": 85, "question": " All right.  Ive decided.  Ill get a kitten.  Want to come look for one with me thi", "qSentId": 84}]
